very recently I have just turned this
$100 into a million dollar over the
course of 90 days and you want to know
what surprised you guys the most it
definitely wasn't when I was about two
weeks away of making the million dollars
by taking 100K to 300 and 300K into a
million it's actually when I turned
these $100 into $3,000 it's the most
viewed and the most watched series every
single time I do the challenge and you
know what that needs me to understand
that you guys are trying it and trying
to take the challenge on for yourself
which I'm absolutely flattered and I
love it and that is the reason for this
video today I'm want to give you the
tips and tricks on how I turned the $800
into $3,000 in the challenge and how you
can turn a small account from 50 to 100
bucks to maybe 500 1,000 or even a
couple of thousand in just 30 days and
now before I start I want to leave
something extremely clear flipping
accounts or growing small accounts is
not going to make you profitable just
because you can take $50 into 500 or
$100 into 1,000 that does not mean that
you are a profitable Trader that just
means that you know how to scale an
account aggressively and quickly but to
become a profitable Trader you have to
learn how to properly manage money and
consistently make profits month after
month flipping accounts and growing
small accounts is not the way to become
a constant profitable Trader this is
something that intermediates and
advanced Traders do on the free time to
just make trading a bit more exciting
because once you're profitable trust me
trading gets very very boring so to
clarify I do not recommend flipping
accounts if you are a beginner or if you
want to make this type of trading your
main source of income flipping is
definitely not the way it's more of the
fun way to bring some spice into the
action of the trading world and secondly
which is probably one of the the most
important things if you want to get into
this flipping game and growing small
accounts is you have to have the new
fisherman mindset now you're probably
asking what the hell does that mean well
they say it's your first time going out
to fish it's your first time buying a
new Rod putting on a hook putting on the
bait into the hook your first time that
you get a rod The Hook and the bait and
you cast it it's probably not the first
time you're going to catch the fish
you're either probably not even fishing
at the right spot the bait comes off the
hook maybe a fish grabs on but you
didn't tie the hook on good enough
there's multiple mistakes that you can
make but it's very easy for you to grab
on and fix to it the same thing is going
to happen to you if it's your first time
growing a small account you might maybe
be trading the right Market or you might
not be trading at the right time or you
don't have the right entry signal and
might just lose the account and I need
you to be on the fisherman mindset
because just because the first time you
cast out the bait and you don't catch a
fish you're not going to just leave and
never try it ever again you're going to
Simply reel back in your h put on
another bait and try it again it's exact
same thing when you're growing a small
account if the first time you end up
blowing your account which is small
amounts of money and should not be
significant to you you just simply try
it again because it's a small account
that you're trying to go you're not
trying to make a living off of this just
doing this for fun and giving a little
spice into trading this is very key to
the longevity of you growing a small
account because you're not emotionally
attached to the money and you're just
doing this to bring some spice into it
you're not doing it to make money you're
doing it to have fun and then obviously
in turn you will make money so now that
we understand that let's go into step
number one which is truthfully the most
important step and if you do this
correctly you're already ahead of the
game of 99% of traders that are going to
try and grow and scale a small account
and I am going to be very
straightforward and very simple with
this Rule and it is as simple as it gets
do not over complicate it do not try to
find a different way around it it's this
and it's this there's nothing around it
step number one is going to be to find
the best possible trade to be your first
trade there's no way around it you need
your first trade to give you the best
entry the minimum draw down and the
maximum risk to reward you're literally
growing a small account the hardest part
is getting out of the hole getting out
from that small $50 balance or a $100
balance to then scale it to a couple
hundred or thousands of dollars you need
to find the perf perfect trade it might
not happen the same week you deposit
into your account it might not even
happen the next week so you have to be
patient waiting for that right trade do
not settle for any trade that is nothing
under perfect because you need the trade
to be able to give you the maximum
amount of profits so then you can
leverage the profits that you make on
your account to then scale without
having to risk all of your money but if
the first trade that you take is going
to be a trade that is uh 5050 end you're
not sure about it do not execute that
trade wait for the best possible trade
scenario again you're not making a
living off of this you're not doing this
for the money you're doing this for fun
to spice up your trading a little bit so
waiting for that right trade is going to
be key to Growing your small account and
getting you out of the hole it could
take four days it can take one day it
can take a week but I want you before
you click the buy or the sell button
when you're going to execute your first
trade want you to ask yourself is this
the best possible trade that I can be
taking at this very moment if the answer
is no then wait for another trade if the
answer is yes double check and then
execute the trade on that very best
trade that you have just found and you
have been waiting for and when I mean
double check I mean double check the
reasons on why you're entering the trade
are you entering the trade because all
of your confluences have been met are
you entering the trade at the right
trading session do you have your entry
signal do you have positive to reward am
I taking an impulsive trade or is this a
real trade that meets my strategy
because at the moment of you being in
front of the market you might be seeing
things that you shouldn't be seeing
because you just want to execute the
trade prior away and be involved into
the market but if right before you click
that buy or sell button you double check
everything which almost gives you a
different reality check and a different
perspective on the market you decide you
know what yeah it does make sense you
know what no I'm making an implosive
decision so double checking is always
key when it comes to taking your first
trade on growing your small account step
number two on growing your small account
which is basically as important as the
first step is going to be holding your
trade I cannot stress to you how many of
you guys will select the first trade the
best possible trade possible but when
you have just made a little bit of money
on your account you close it you cut
your profit so fast and you are
literally defeating the whole purpose of
waiting for the best possible trade when
you wait for the best possible trade
that meets your checklist and meets your
trading plan it is literally for you to
maximize those profits don't rest for a
one to one risk to reward or even a one
to2 risk reward aim for the 1 to three
one to four 1 to 5 this is what waiting
for the best possible trade is the
outcome of maximizing your profits and
minimizing your losses you want to make
sure that you can hold as long as you
possibly can because once you risk your
account on your first trade you want to
make sure you can maximize it as much as
you can so when you close out at the max
profits you have you then you do not
have to then risk all of that money
again on the next trade so you want to
maximize your profits so then you have
more money into the account that won't
overexpose you and take you back to the
end step and maximizing your profits is
is really different depending on the
type of trade that you're doing if
you're taking a day trade you should be
looking for a 1 to four to a 1 to 5 to a
1 to six if you're swing trading you
should be aiming for a 1 to 5 1 to six 1
to 7 risk reward you want to make sure
that you can maximize the most amount of
profit out of the trade that you're
taking now keep in mind if you're taking
a scalp trade can't really expect to
have a 1 to seven risk to reward just
because of the nature of the market does
not end up giving you those type of
moves so depending on the type of trade
that you're taking make sure you can
maximize the amount of risk to reward
that you're going to be having inside of
that strategy now we all have different
strategies and we all have different
ways on looking the market I'm going to
explain to you next on how I do it but
you got to make sure that you are
familiar with the type of trade that
you're taking so you know how to then
maximize the profits there and another
little hack that I have for you guys to
maximize your profits is going to be to
always close your trades at the end of
New York session and They Might Be
Wondering Why well at the end of New
York session is literally at the end of
all the push the market has had and
that's where you're going to maximize
your profits because if you enter a
trade in London and then you hold
throughout London and let's say you
close at the end of London beginning of
New York there is a whole new volume and
if you have the right direction of the
market then that session is going to
continue to push a trade into your favor
how many times have you close the trade
and as soon as you close it the trade
keeps going into your takeprofit and
then you miss out on all those profits
that sucks it's happened to me and I
hate it and the way I've learned to
maximize the profit is by waiting into
the end of the day on New York session
to close out on the trade because that
is when all the move is done and you're
able to close out at the final trade
that the market has done and step three
is probably the hardest one which is
going to be repeated all you literally
have to do is repeat step number one and
step number two that is literally what I
did over the course of 3 months turning
$800 into a million now it's very hard
to obviously wait for those perfect
trades and I know it's very hard to then
hold them as much as you can but it's
even harder for them you to be patient
to wait for those next trades but I
promise you that as soon as you enter
into that flow and you enter into that
mindset and you start normalizing taking
these type of Trades only then you're
going to see how much your small account
is going to grow so much faster
exponentially because you're simply
taking the highest probability trade
posses and the highest probability trade
posses the way I do it and the way I
analyze it are going to be off of three
basic foundations and I do this for
every single one of my trades on my
personal accounts on my growing accounts
on my flipping the 100 into the mill
these three things are exactly what I
did you can go see it for yourself in
the 100 to the mill series that I have
done step number one and the most
important is going to be two consecutive
time frames insane for example if you
want to buy the market you want to have
the weekly and the daily in your favor
that are bullish if the weekly and the
we the weekly is bullish the day is
bearish and the 4H hour is bullish you
have three markets that are all over the
place there's no consecutive time frames
you should not be interested in the
trade you should only in be interested
in the trade if you have either the
weekly bullish the daily bullish and
let's say the four hours bearish that's
fine because you have two consecutive
time frames in syn to the upside and
they buy or let's say you have the
weekly bearish but the daily bullish and
the 4-Hour bullish this is good because
you have two consecutive time frames in
sync heading in the direction that you
would want to now obviously the same
thing would happen if you were selling
if you have the weekly bullish but then
the daily and the 4H hour are bearish
that's fine because you have two
consecutive time frames in the same
direction to them so having the
consecutive time frame is you trading
with the trend we've all heard the term
the trend is your friend and trust me it
is so for example you can take Euro JPY
where I started off the week saying that
I wanted to make $250,000 by the end of
the week and I didn't because I
literally waited for the market to give
me the two consecutive time frames and
say this is going to be key for you guys
to understand that you don't always have
to wait for three time frames but you
need to have a minimum of two and in
this case we ended up holding the trade
for about 3 days and we got about a 1 to
2.5 ver two reward where we made A4
million you don't always have to wait
for three time frames in sync two time
frames is more than enough but two time
frames is not enough to just execute the
trade you're going to need the next
point which is going to be area of
Interest where are you going to be
entering the trade in this market that's
bullish or in this market that's bearish
if the market is bullish you need to
find a key level to then buy
if the market is bearish you need to
find a key level to then sell just
because the Market's bullish you can't
just buy because the Market's going up
or the Market's going down you can't
just sell because the Market's going
down you have to wait for a very precise
pullback into a specific Zone where then
there you're going to apply the next
step but the area of interest is even as
important as the trend because if you
don't have price pull back into this
area you do not execute the trade the
best analogy that I can put to this is
is when you are going to let's say buy a
an investment let's say you're going to
buy a real estate investment you don't
ever want to buy at the high of the
market let's say you're going to buy a
property for $100,000 and that is the
maximum that the home is valued at in
that neighborhood that's not a great
investment you want to wait for the
property to have some type of time in
the market so then you have room for
negotiation and you can make an offer
for let's say $80,000 and then if you
were to make an offer for $80,000 after
after 2 months of it being on the market
and nobody else has bought it and you
make the offer for 80 and they accept it
visually on the chart what you see is
price go up to 100,000 then retrace to
80 that's where you buy and then you
hold for the next year or two and then
the price continues to go up you're
waiting for the discount on the real
estate it's the exact same thing on the
market when the market is bullish you're
waiting for the pullback that is the
discount that you're going to be waiting
to the market so then you execute the
trade and then you buy so on this
discount that you're waiting for the
market as soon as you start seeing that
retracement and it's going into the area
of interest you then need the reason on
why you're going to enter so it's going
to be known as the entry signal now in
trading there's many different types of
Entry signals but the ones that I use
are going to be the most important to me
in my strategy and the most powerful
that I have seen over the last course of
seven years of trading the market first
one is going to be morning star
formation and evening star formation and
now the key of these two patterns is
that it happens at the area of Interest
not almost at the area of Interest or
away from the area of interest is at the
area of Interest once price has made it
to the area of where it's the perfect
discount then you have the entry signal
there then you take the trade you do not
take the trade even if you have the
entry signal if it's not at the area of
Interest this is going to be very key
for you to avoid Wick outs fake outs
liquidity grabs all these different type
of excuses that Traders put into the
market on why they got stopped out I
barely ever get Wicked out or stopped
out because I wait for the trade to make
it to the area of interest and the best
analogy that I can put on these entry
signals it's as if you are interested in
buying this home for 100,000 price is
starting to retrace and have a pullback
and get a discount of 80,000 and the
reason for you to enter that investment
is that a home Five Doors Down just sold
for9
$5,000 and that current house you're
looking to invest into is still priced
at 80 that is your entry signal meaning
if you buy this property the comparables
around you are going up which makes it a
great investment this is very similar in
the markets but you're going to have
that entry signal or that confirmation
of the next property being sold at a
higher price when you have these entry
signal confirmations but again the most
important thing is that you have the
entry signal at the area entrance and
lastly is going to be the risk
management risk management is key to
this because obviously you're growing a
small account you need to obviously have
a proper risk management and truthfully
let's be honest there's no real real
real risk management here there's no
real 1% 2% you're never going to grow a
small account like this you're not going
to risk 1% of $100 you're not going to
risk $1 respectfully it just won't make
sense of your time and it's not going to
be worth your head space and effort
you're going to put into the market the
first trade you're going to take has to
be 100% risk of the account if you are
not okay with risking $100 then you are
not ready to grow a small account this
is meant for people that are okay with
risking $100 and it does not affect them
financially and it's not a financial
burtom into their statements there's
going to be just for the first trade
you're going to risk 100% maximize your
profits and then on the following trades
you're then going to be risking anywhere
from 30 to then 50% if you win the next
trade and then you get a 1 to 3 1 to 4
then every trade after that you're going
to risk 20 to 25% but no more than 20 to
25% this is going to be very key to then
successfully staying positive on the
account because if you were to say let's
say you start off with $100 then you
take it to about 4 to 500 then you risk
50% of that so then you're risking 200
bucks and you got another one to three
now you have just turned the account
balance of four 400 into about 1,000 and
then you can just risk 20% of that which
you're risking 200 bucks per trade this
is very Key by simply risking 100% on
the first trade 50% on the second and
then 20 to 25 on the third and so on and
most importantly is to have a take
profit of your account my goal is to
take this $100 into 500 or take this 100
into 1,000 or 4,000 5,000 whatever goal
it is that you want to take be istic to
it and once you get there withdraw the
money and do it again do not get greedy
do not want and try to make more money
than you should stay to the plan and do
not break it for anything the ingredient
the markets will mess up everything that
you've done and these take profits are
things that I do every single week for
my personal account literally on this
Euro JPY trade I started off the week
saying you know what I want to make
$250,000 for the week the trade hit
exactly
$251,000 and I could have gotten lot
more profit but that's all that I wanted
for the week these are things that I
constantly do with my students every
single Sunday when I break down the
exact same trades that I'm taking where
I'm going to be making profits like
these and profits like these I literally
share with them every single Sunday on a
call that we get called Sunday swings
where I break down every single trade on
what I'm looking to do where I'm looking
to enter and where I'm looking to get
out they have access to my full strategy
and part of the private disc gr
Community if you want to learn more
about the set and forget strategy and
how it's made me hundreds of thousands
of dollars make sure you guys check out
the link in the description below
because it's where I'm going to be
getting on weekly calls with my students
sharing my trades hope you guys hit that
like And subscribe button and we will
see you guys in the next one